Why do you have
to keep your worries
about Jin Ho to yourself?
You can tell Joey.
No, I don't want to bother her.
It's her family time.
I noticed you and Andrew
are close.
Now that I know him,
he's actually kind.
You're blushing, Joey.
This is the coordination letter.
I've also referred you
to the Drug Enforcement Unit
in the North, located
in the town of Balmora.
Are you spying on me?
Whatever you heard,
it can't get out.
What's going on
in the town of Balmora?
Don't worry, if I find out,
I'll tell you.
I have to go now.
Just leave tomorrow.
Dad, I'm going to give you
something.
This is cute.
I'll go ahead.
- Be careful, okay?
- Okay.
Don't worry, Berdugo.
We've prepared everything
for him.
Make sure this won't fail.
You can count on it, Berdugo.
Just think it's his first day on
the job,
and his last day on earth.
- Berdugo.
- Don't let it drag on.
- Finish him off.
- Sure, Boss.
Don't involve my family!
Do you want to save your family?
You're going to die!
Chief sent me here
to give you this.
This is Miguel's badge.
Why is it burned?
They say a car exploded
on the Bolagos highway.
They say the victim
is a police officer.
Where is Miguel?
It looks like Miguel was
involved in the explosion.
That can't be true!
My husband just left!
Take us to Dad, please!
Is this all the evidence
you got, huh?
Nothing else?
Nothing, Sir.
Ma'am, this way.
Move aside.
Move.
Here, Ma'am.
Joey...
Sir...
Dad...
Is that Dad?
Can I see him first?
Joey, it's not a good idea
to see your father like this.
You can't approach him.
The plate number
has been confirmed,
as well as the personal effects
that were taken.
Everything belongs to Miguel.
I'm sorry, Clarissa, Joey.
Can't I really see him first?
Not yet.
Go ahead, sit down first.
Dad, I'm going to give you
something...
so you won't forget mom and me.
I really won't forget you,
but this is cute.
Mom, this is what I gave Dad.
Boss Idol.
I know Major Miguel Delgado.
Let him in.
This way.
Joey...
Andrew...
It's dad...
Chief, where are you taking
the remains?
To the crime lab for autopsy.
Standard procedure.
Can't we see him...
before you do that?
Joey, Miguel's remains
are severely burned.
It's better if you don't see him
in that condition.
And based on
the initial findings,
there is a possibility
of foul play,
so we don't want to contaminate
the evidence before the autopsy.
After the process,
we will release
the remains to you.
So it would be better for you to
go home and rest.
Just a second...
How did you know
it was really dad...
if the body was so badly burned?
Through the plate number
and personal effects.
But we will still conduct
a DNA test for verification.
Chief, what do you mean
by foul play?
At first glance,
it looks like an accident.
There are skid marks
on the road.
It looks like he lost control
before he hit the wall.
But we found a shell casing
at the crash site,
And it's not from Miguel's
service firearm.
That means there is a shooter.
It's a targeted attack.
And it looks like he made sure
Miguel won't survive.
I told him not to return
to the service!
If he hadn't left,
this wouldn't have happened!
What's the news?
Boss...
his family is here...
crying.
Are you sure Delgado is dead?
I was only a few meters away
when his car exploded.
Delgado was inside,
so I'm sure he's dead.
Good.
I'll increase your pay
for a job well done.
Thank you, Berdugo.
Poor Delgado.
He ended up
looking like a "sisig."
He's fond of explosions,
after all.
He got what he deserved.
Cruz, bring them home.
- Ma'am, let's go.
- No, Cruz, I'll do it.
I'll handle it.
Let's go.
Joey, I'm sorry for
what happened.
But I promise we'll help
with the investigation
as much as we need to.
Thanks, but...
there's no need to...
because the body is subject for
a DNA test, right?
It's not yet certain
that it's really Dad.
Who knows, he survived, right?
Dad might still be alive.
From the look of the car,
whoever was inside
would have been badly burned.
It's definitely unrecognizable.
But based on the personal
effects,
there's no other possible victim
but Major Miguel Delgado.
I mean, who else, right?
Elai, enough.
Joey, sorry. I didn't mean it.
I was just basing it...
- on facts.
- That's enough.
Stop, stop, stop.
It's okay.
But it's probably
not that bad...
to hope Dad is still alive,
right?
Because he said...
this is...
his last mission,
and then...
he's going to retire.
And...
he said we'll be together
with mom.
And I believe dad
could still be alive.
Because they'll still have
his body be DNA tested?
So while, while there's
no proof yet,
I believe dad is still alive.
He might not be dead yet.
Right, Mom?
Joey...
Dad...
Just one stand-upper,
then go home.
Then I'll go with you to edit.
Copy, copy.
Okay, I'll take care of it.
Thanks.
Andrew...
Is Joey mad at me?
She's grieving.
It's good that you're here.
Well, you didn't just come here
for news.
It's obvious that you
really care for Joey.
I was surprised.
You're not usually like this
with our subjects.
She's not just a subject.
We've been through
a lot together.
I've also met her family.
So yes, we've become
really close.
If you're asking me
if I'm affected,
I'm affected.
Yes, it shows.
You really want to know
what happened to Major Delgado.
Come on, let's finish this.
Let's go.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Game?
Ready?
Camera.
Rolling.
Five, four, three...
A Bolagos Police officer
is suspected of being killed
in an explosion incident
along the Service Road tonight.
According to authorities,
it is believed
that Major Miguel Delgado
of the Bolagos Police is the
victim
after identifying
the burned out vehicle
and some personal belongings
recovered from the scene
of the incident.
In an interview with Police
Chief Lansang of Bolagos,
at first glance,
it seemed like an accident,
but there is evidence
that suggests
foul play was possible.
The victim's remains have been
brought to the crime laboratory
for DNA confirmation.
My god...
Hon...
have you seen this?
What is it?
Bad news?
Miguel, Clarissa's husband,
died last night.
His vehicle exploded!
Is this tragedy still connected
to the alleged syndicate?
That's what we're going
to find out, Ka-Tiradas.
Hey! Peter, you're driving me
crazy!
I've been looking for you
for some time now.
Where did you come from?
You didn't even answer
my calls and texts.
You know, you're so noisy.
You know, I'm already annoyed
with Jin Ho's landlady,
You're going to add to that.
You're so noisy.
Jin Ho's landlady?
Yes.
I went to his old house to ask.
Do you know what happened?
I even ended up ebing the one
they took their anger out on.
She said there was so much trash
Jin Ho left behind
that it was hard to clean up.
What? Is it my fault?
You know, Andrew's right.
We don't really know
that Korean.
Think about it, he passed by,
wreaked havoc,
and then he suddenly left.
Oh, you're so great.
You're so deep.
What? Wreaked havoc?
What's that? Typhoon?
Then who are you?
Sierra Madre?
But admit it, just admit it.
You made an effort.
Right, wrong?
Of course, I'm worried, right?
I thought we were friends.
but it turns out I was the only
one who thought of that.
Wait, what do you need?
Why are you looking for me?
What's that?
Look, this is the car
of Joey's dad.
It's like...
it's like someone
really killed him.
Mom, you should rest first.
You too, Joey, okay?
Peter?
Joey...
Joey, I heard about
what happened.
How are you?
How is Auntie?
I'll just ask permission from my
uncle, and then I'll go there.
No, that's not necessary.
Why?
Well, Father's body hasn't been
released yet,
they say they still need
an autopsy
to make sure he was the victim.
I hope he's not,
because I feel sorry for
Uncle if that were the case.
All his battles were
for the good.
His story shouldn't have
ended like this.
That's why I don't believe it.
What do you mean, Joey?
I don't know, Peter,
but I have a really strong
feeling
that Dad is still alive.
So until I see his body,
I won't believe it's him.
I will never lose hope
that my father is still alive.
Mother, I'll take care of that.
No, no, I'll take care of it.
I'm just removing the dirt
from the glass.
Because it won't come off.
Why won't it come off?
This isn't working.
We don't know...
how to arrange the wake
of your father.
We don't know...
what he'll look like when
he comes back to us anymore.
Mother, do you really believe
that Dad is really dead?
Don't you want to hope
that he's still alive?
I want to, Joey.
I really want to hope
that he's alive.
But how after what we saw?
His life has been in danger
several times,
but he always makes it home.
But now...
But Joey, it seems impossible.
Still no update
on Major Delgado's autopsy.
That's the thing.
Twelve hours have passed.
I thought they would
expedite it,
knowing that this is
a high-profile case.
I'm sure Joey is also waiting
for an answer.
What did Major Delgado's body
look like
after the explosion?
Was it really unrecognizable?
Actually, we didn't see it.
They took the body very
carefully and privately
out of respect
for Major Delgado.
They also made sure
that the family didn't see it.
because they might not be able
to handle it.
So no one saw it
except the police?
This, this is okay.
This is okay too.
This too.
But this, something is missing.
Better yet, complete it first
and then return it to me, okay?
Okay, Sir,
I'll just fix it again.
Sir, how long will
the autopsy take?
What else do they need to do?
Why can't we get Dad's remains?
Joey, you have to understand
that there was foul play
in what happened to Miguel.
There's a lot that needs
to be investigated,
and it needs to be done
carefully and slowly,
especially since the state of
your Dad's remains is dangerous.
Well, Sir, but...
- Perez.
- Sir?
Where's the report
I'm asking you to take care of?
Oh, here it is, Sir.
- Here, Sir.
- This is important.
This is missing a signatory.
Yes, Sir, I'll just
follow up again.
- Okay, Sir.
- Thank you.
But, Sir, the autopsies probably
know what they're doing,
so they know how long
the tests will take.
Why can't they give us a
definite time
when we can see Dad?
Joey...
I can't really say right now.
Don't be in a hurry, okay?
This is for your dad.
Go home,
watch over Clarissa,
and we'll take care of this.
Ah, I'm sorry.
I have to go somewhere else.
- Oh, Perez.
- Sir?
Leo's case.
- Yes, Sir.
- Investigate it, okay?
Yes, I'll follow it up
right away.
Hello, Sir Emerson,
I'm on my way there.
Peter.
Sir?
It's me, Jin Ho.
Jin Ho?
Jin Ho , what happened to you?
Where are you?
That's why I can't contact you,
you changed your number!
Peter, listen.
I only called to tell you...
do not contact me again.
Huh? What are you saying?
Jin Ho, you need to know
something.
This is last time we talk.
Something happened
to Joey's father.
He's gone!
What?
Joey's father is dead, Jin Ho.
Nothing?
Joey!
What are you doing here?
Chief, where's Dad?
Why is his body not here?
I just have a strong hunch.
I believe dad is still alive.
If your dad is alive,
why hasn't he come home
to you yet, right?
If I only knew where he went.
You guys have finalized
the deal, huh?
Once we meet,
the deal is sealed.
Just tell me about
Joey's father.
He needs us now, Jin Ho.
I can't, I haven't found
her yet.
Any news on Major Delgado's
DNA or autopsy?
You know the protocol.
Sir, how long are we going
to keep this?
If anyone knows where he went,
it's Lansang.
Drug syndicate?